<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522190000 -0400" stop="20260522193000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>The family must figure out how to keep the restaurant open after Bob's flattop breaks on the morning of the Ocean Avenue Business Association's: Ocean Fest on Ocean Avenue.</desc><sub-title>Bob Belcher and the Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Kids</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522185744 -0400" stop="20260522192212 -0400"><title>The Great North</title><desc>Beef and Wolf meet their hero, legendary mountain man, Tusk Johnson! Judy and the rest of the Tobin clan become addicted to '80s primetime soap "Dynasty".</desc><sub-title>Tusk in the Wind Adventure</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522191907 -0400" stop="20260522205222 -0400"><title>Shrek</title><desc>It ain't easy bein' green -- especially if you're a likable (albeit smelly) ogre named Shrek. On a mission to retrieve a gorgeous princess from the clutches of a fire-breathing dragon, Shrek teams up with an unlikely compatriot -- a wisecracking donkey.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523000000 +0100" stop="20260523003000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 53</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522191126 -0400" stop="20260522193913 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>It's Alistair and Emma Mundell's turn to host in sleepy Lynton, North Devon at their four-star premises which only opened three months ago.

The B&amp;B newbies are desperate to impress with their recently renovated rooms. The accommodation proves a winner with Mark and Fee and John and Neil, but Mrs Tee is proving more difficult to please.

Later a ride on the Victorian cliff railway from Lynton to Lynmouth proves hard for two of their guests who are afraid of heights.

Over dinner John and Neil reveal their B&amp;B is in Blackpool - a town which which Alistair confesses is his `worst nightmare'.

In the morning Mrs Tee says she didn't sleep because of traffic noise and is so critical of the cooked breakfast the other guests are reduced to hysterics.</desc><sub-title>Castle Hill Guesthouse, Lynton</sub-title></programme></tv>