<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518141300 -0400" stop="20260518161500 -0400"><title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title><desc>After stealing a mysterious orb in the far reaches of outer space, Peter Quill from Earth is now the main target of a manhunt led by the villain known as Ronan the Accuser. To help fight Ronan and his team and save the galaxy from his power, Quill creates a team of space heroes known as the "Guardians of the Galaxy" to save the galaxy.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518144548 -0400" stop="20260518151038 -0400"><title>New Girl</title><desc>Jess gets jealous when Winston joins her troubled-youth handbell quartet and instantly becomes a natural. Meanwhile Nick and Schmidt engage in class warfare when the toilet breaks and they each have their own idea of how to get it fixed.</desc><sub-title>Bells</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260518141121 -0400" stop="20260518154657 -0400"><title>Toy Story 2</title><desc>While Andy is away at cowboy camp Woody has been toynapped by Al McWiggin, a greedy collector and proprietor of "Al's Toy Barn". In this all-out rescue mission, Buzz and his friends Mr. Potato Head, Slinky Dog, Rex and Hamm spring into action to rescue Woody from winding up as a museum piece. They must find a way to save him before he gets sold in Japan forever and they'll never see him again.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260518190000 +0100" stop="20260518200500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>Former F1 World Champion Damon Hill sets a time in the Liana as a Racing Driver in a Reasonably Priced Car. The Aston Martin DB5 and Jaguar E-Type are compared; the snipers of the Irish Guards try to shoot Jeremy as he drives the new Mercedes SLK and the new Porsche Boxster 2 around a deserted village. James drives the new 4x4 from Nissan, the Murano and Richard travels to Italy to drive the Maserati Gran Sport around the Maserati test track.</desc><sub-title>Clarkson Compares the Boxster S and SLK 55 Under Sniper Fire</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518144703 -0400" stop="20260518151450 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>It's the last day of the competition and the rivals find out who will be crowned best value B&amp;B of the week. Scores are settled concerning cleanliness, and a morning cuppa gets a roasting.</desc><sub-title>Four In A Bed</sub-title></programme></tv>