<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523000000 -0400" stop="20260523003000 -0400"><title>Two and a Half Men</title><desc>Zoey tries to convince Walden to cut his hair and shave; Alan and Lyndsey revive their relationship.</desc><sub-title>A Possum on Chemo</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522235829 -0400" stop="20260523002411 -0400"><title>How I Met Your Mother</title><desc>Marshall interns at the corporation where Barney works and Lily finds that he is becoming a shallow jerk as he tries to fit in with his crude fratty coworkers. Meanwhile, Ted feels guilty when he receives several gifts from Victoria (Erika Singh) while he hasn't sent her anything.</desc><sub-title>Life Among the Gorillas</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522223004 -0400" stop="20260523010000 -0400"><title>Bad Boys II</title><desc>Miami is being flooded with ecstasy that's coming from Cuba through drug lord Johnny Tapia. Detectives Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett are on the case, and are determined to bring the man to justice. Additional drama is provided by friction with the DEA, which counts Marcus' younger sister Sydney among its agents, and from Marcus possibly transferring out of the department, leaving Mike without his longtime partner.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523050000 +0100" stop="20260523053000 +0100"><title>The Joy of Painting</title><desc>Guest Artist Joyce Ortner captures the true beauty of the ocean waves, blue and enchanting in this breathtaking seascape masterpiece.</desc><sub-title>Anatomy of a Wave</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522235847 -0400" stop="20260523002632 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The hosts meet for one last time to find out what they've been paid and to thrash out their differences.

There's soon trouble as Mrs Tee finds out that it's Alistair and Emma who scored her only one lowly point for cleanliness.

The confrontation continues when the roles are reversed with a heated exchange resulting in a walk out.</desc><sub-title>Payment Day, Week 2</sub-title></programme></tv>