<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517010000 -0400" stop="20260517014500 -0400"><title>24</title><desc>Jack initiates a fierce gun battle with the terrorists as he races to rescue Heller and Audrey before the military strike begins.

Dina questions her own dedication to their cause when her husband reveals his plans for Behrooz.

Driscoll and Curtis uncover new evidence that points to an even bigger attack by the terrorists.

Audrey has an awkward meeting with her husband, and Heller butts heads once again with his son.</desc><sub-title>Day 4: 12:00 P.M.-1:00 P.M.</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517012141 -0400" stop="20260517014704 -0400"><title>New Girl</title><desc>The guys are invited to a wedding, and Nick is fearful that he'll run into his ex, so he asks Jess to be his date. Meanwhile, Winston takes his role as usher very seriously, and Schmidt catches the eye of two women.</desc><sub-title>Wedding</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517003711 -0400" stop="20260517021942 -0400"><title>Shaun of the Dead</title><desc>Shaun (Simon Pegg) doesn't have a very good day, so he decides to turn his life around by getting his ex to take him back, but he times it for right in the middle of what may be a zombie apocalypse. But for him, it's an opportunity to show everyone he knows how useful he is by saving them all. All he has to do is survive, and get his ex back.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517063000 +0100" stop="20260517070000 +0100"><title>My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic</title><desc>Starlight Glimmer leads an unlikely squad of rescuers against one of the ponies' oldest and greatest foes in order to save her friends and Equestria.</desc><sub-title>To Where and Back Again (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517004014 -0400" stop="20260517013156 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Jamie and Adam answer the burning barnyard myth - can a hurricane blow the feathers off a chicken? Meanwhile, Grant, Tory and Kari embrace their sadistic sides and turn the workshop into a horticultural house of horrors.</desc><sub-title>Deadly Straw</sub-title></programme></tv>