<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530161500 -0400" stop="20260530170000 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>Monk has been killed by his friend, Stottlemeyer. or has he? The captain helped Monk fake his death, so they can track down whose been framing Monk. Monk has to hide out while Stottlemeyer works the case. Since only Stottlemeyer knows he's alive, Natalie proceeds with the funeral arrangements.</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk Is on the Run (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530165100 -0400" stop="20260530171440 -0400"><title>The Big Bang Theory</title><desc>When their apartment is robbed, Leonard and Sheldon turn to their friends to create a state-of-the-art security system.</desc><sub-title>The Bozeman Reaction</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530164832 -0400" stop="20260530172551 -0400"><title>The Boy, the Mole, the Fox and the Horse</title><desc>Charlie Mackesy's bestselling book comes to life in this beautifully animated film from NoneMore and Bad Robot Productions. Follow the unlikely bond between four friends as they explore the meaning of kindness, friendship, courage and hope. A story for viewers of all ages in a heartwarming, classically animated film.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530210000 +0100" stop="20260530220000 +0100"><title>Doctor Who (2005)</title><desc>One year has passed since the events of "The Sound of Drums." The Earth has been conquered and its population enslaved, the Doctor is the Master's prisoner, and the warships of a new Time Lord Empire rise from the ashes. The fate of the world is in Martha Jones' hands.</desc><sub-title>Last of the Time Lords (3)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530163306 -0400" stop="20260530170036 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>It's the last day of the competition and the rival B&amp;B owners meet to settle some scores and discover what they've been paid.

Kicking things off is Knockaloe Beg farm on the Isle of Man, and hosts Fiona and John Anderson tackle criticisms of a missing host at breakfast.

Next, Phil Routledge from The Arches on the Isle of Man takes on Robbie and John Welling from the Trafford in Blackpool about their forensic investigation, but holds his hands up about the fact they stumbled upon his personal walk-in wardrobe.

Next, Robbie and John want to get a straight answer from Phil on why he wouldn't be up for a return visit.

The last host, Julie Brogan from Sheepy Lodge in the Midlands, discovers that she's more apologetic than she thought and realises that sorry is the hardest word for her guests to hear.

With all the payments finally revealed, the winner is announced.</desc><sub-title>Payment Day</sub-title></programme></tv>