<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522200000 -0400" stop="20260522203000 -0400"><title>The Last Man on Earth</title><desc>Along with most human life, the virus wiped out normal traditions and holidays. As Christmas approaches, Carol spearheads a &#8220;Secret Santa&#8221; gift exchange to spread some festive cheer.</desc><sub-title>Secret Santa</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522201009 -0400" stop="20260522203515 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>Michael starts monitoring the emails sent out in the Dunder-Mifflin workplace, upsetting the employees. Meanwhile, Pam believes that the relationship between Dwight and Angela is more than just worker to worker, Jim throws an office BBQ at his house in order to show his roommate the kinds of people he deals with everyday, and Michael, after annoying everyone at his improv classes, crashes Jim's party with a terrible karaoke number.</desc><sub-title>Email Surveillance</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522191907 -0400" stop="20260522205222 -0400"><title>Shrek</title><desc>It ain't easy bein' green -- especially if you're a likable (albeit smelly) ogre named Shrek. On a mission to retrieve a gorgeous princess from the clutches of a fire-breathing dragon, Shrek teams up with an unlikely compatriot -- a wisecracking donkey.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523010000 +0100" stop="20260523013000 +0100"><title>Fate/stay night</title><desc>A fleeing Shir&#333; is eventually cornered by Rin, who offers to spare his life if he gives her his Command Seals. However, he refuses, prompting Rin to try and kill him. Both are then distracted by a scream downstairs and he and Rin find an unconscious girl. As Rin attempts to heal her, a dagger flies through an open door, aimed for Rin, but Shir&#333; blocks it with his arm, wounding himself in the process. He runs outside to find the female Servant, which is of the Rider class, and repels an attack by her. Shir&#333; considers summoning Saber via Command Seal, but decides it is too risky to get her involved and resolves to confront Rider himself. Rider resumes her assault, and Shir&#333; is nearly killed by her until Rin rescues him. At Rin's home, Shir&#333; and Rin decide to form a temporary truce to find Rider's Master.</desc><sub-title>Two Magi (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522193913 -0400" stop="20260522203227 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Britain's famous Lake District is where tourists are plentiful and money is flowing. However, the Glass House Restaurant in Ambleside seems to have missed both points.</desc><sub-title>The Glass House</sub-title></programme></tv>