<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260525063000 -0400" stop="20260525070000 -0400"><title>Cheers</title><desc>Rebecca and Sam both have mixed emotions as they face the fact that Robin Colcord, after proposing to Rebecca, is arrested for insider trading based on information supplied by the once and future owner of Cheers.</desc><sub-title>Cry Harder (2)</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260525061312 -0400" stop="20260525074029 -0400"><title>Idiocracy</title><desc>Corporal Joe Bauers, a decidedly average American, is selected for a top-secret hibernation program but is forgotten and left to awaken to a future so incredibly moronic that he's easily the most intelligent person alive.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260525051717 -0400" stop="20260525070032 -0400"><title>A Fistful of Dollars</title><desc>The Man With No Name enters the Mexican village of San Miguel in the midst of a power struggle among the three Rojo brothers and sheriff John Baxter. When a regiment of Mexican soldiers bearing gold intended to pay for new weapons is waylaid by the Rojo brothers, the stranger inserts himself into the middle of the long-simmering battle, selling false information to both sides for his own benefit.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260525063712 -0400" stop="20260525072914 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Adam and Jamie put on wetsuits and get ready to take a dive for another myth busting experiment. Is it possible to lift a sunken boat from the ocean floor using only ping pong balls? The MythBusters try to salvage the MythTanic-2 with ping pong balls.</desc><sub-title>Pingpong Rescue</sub-title></programme></tv>