<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523174500 -0400" stop="20260523183000 -0400"><title>Monk</title><desc>Monk becomes a social pariah when he shoots a man dressed as Santa Claus. Can he clear his name and foil a larger criminal plot in time for Christmas?</desc><sub-title>Mr. Monk and the Man Who Shot Santa Claus</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523180359 -0400" stop="20260523182833 -0400"><title>New Girl</title><desc>While training for a marathon, Jess discovers that Cece has been keeping a secret from her, and their friendship is put to the test. Meanwhile, Winston can't handle being the only one who knows about Cece and Schmidt, and Nick reluctantly asks for Schmidt's help as he tries to juggle dating two women at once.</desc><sub-title>Secrets</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523164257 -0400" stop="20260523184506 -0400"><title>1917</title><desc>April 6th, 1917. As an infantry battalion assembles to wage war deep in enemy territory, two soldiers are assigned to race against time and deliver a message that will stop 1,600 men from walking straight into a deadly trap.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523230000 +0100" stop="20260523233000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Conway visits the CAD room and others to try and encourage people to talk about their problems.  June asks Conway what he thinks her chances are of becoming a Sgt.  After being wound up by Sgt Penny, Taffy talks to Conway about getting a transfer out of Sunhill as his wife is not liking the city.   Claire and Taffy visit the parents of a missing girl before they start on a door-to-door in the neighbourhood.  Claire thinks she has found a witness until her son says she was in a home when the girl was last seen.  While door knocking, a car alarm causes frayed tempers.  When the owner refuses to turn off the alarm, the car is vandalised.  Girl is later found in the market.</desc><sub-title>Communications</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523180600 -0400" stop="20260523183347 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>Jessica and Adrian Rashleigh hope the beautiful Cornish coastal surroundings will make up for the snugness of their three bed outfit in St Ives. Will their guests agree?

For the activity, Jessica and Adrian take their guests on a magical mystery camper van tour of the local sights. At breakfast some of the guests struggle with the small breakfast room, but the food itself goes down quite well. And later, so do the men, as Eileen demonstrates her karate skills by flooring every one of them.</desc><sub-title>Chy Conyn, St. Ives</sub-title></programme></tv>