<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260601025500 -0400" stop="20260601032000 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Monica and Chandler disagree over how to redecorate Rachel's old room. Joey advertises for a "non-ugly" roommate. Ross is unwilling to accept that he still has feelings for Rachel.</desc><sub-title>The One with Ross's Denial</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260601030537 -0400" stop="20260601045703 -0400"><title>Deadpool</title><desc>This is the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter ego Deadpool. Armed with his new abilities and a dark, twisted sense of humor, Deadpool hunts down the man who nearly destroyed his life.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260601024311 -0400" stop="20260601042406 -0400"><title>Elio</title><desc>Elio, a space fanatic with an active imagination, finds himself on a cosmic misadventure where he must form new bonds with alien lifeforms, navigate a crisis of intergalactic proportions and somehow discover who he is truly meant to be.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260601080000 +0100" stop="20260601083000 +0100"><title>The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title><desc>A family friend visits Philip. He asks WIll to do something illegal and Will tries to find a way to avoid the issue. Carlton and Hilary try to find a match in online dating and end up being matched with each other.</desc><sub-title>To Thine Own Self Be Blue... and Gold</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260601030835 -0400" stop="20260601033249 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Wood Windows, Woven Cashmere Fabric, Plastic Recycling Machines, and Architectural Glass and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Wood Windows, Woven Cashmere Fabric, Plastic Recycling Machines, Architectural Glass</sub-title></programme></tv>