<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531080000 -0400" stop="20260531083000 -0400"><title>The Nanny</title><desc>Fran's old nemesis lands a role on a popular soap opera.</desc><sub-title>The Heather Biblow Story</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531075657 -0400" stop="20260531082148 -0400"><title>The Office (US)</title><desc>Jan told Michael that the board had voted to close the Scranton branch. There would be a select group of employees that would get a severance package; the others would be going to work at the Stamford branch. She informed Michael that he would be one who would get a severance package.</desc><sub-title>Branch Closing</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531074045 -0400" stop="20260531095941 -0400"><title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title><desc>After saving Xandar from Ronan's wrath, the Guardians are now recognized as heroes. Now the team must help their leader, Star Lord, uncover the truth behind his true heritage. Along the way, old foes turn to allies and betrayal is blooming. And the Guardians find they are up against a devastating new menace who is out to rule the galaxy.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531130000 +0100" stop="20260531133000 +0100"><title>Lucky Star</title><desc>It is summertime for the girls; that means one thing: comfortable summer uniforms!  Tsukasa and Kagami are fraternal twins, but Konata shows them the similar and different characteristics they share. Konata, Kagami, and Tsukasa each try to put their hair into a ponytail, just to see who looks best. Unfortunately, Kagami is the only one who cannot pull it off.</desc><sub-title>Different Kinds of People</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531073445 -0400" stop="20260531082142 -0400"><title>Richard Hammond's BIG</title><desc>Richard explores the huge Tottenham Hotspur Football Stadium in London. He explores a pitch that splits and rolls away and takes a terrifying walk on the stadium roof!</desc><sub-title>Super Stadium</sub-title></programme></tv>