<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260517070000 -0400" stop="20260517073000 -0400"><title>Cheers</title><desc>Frasier and the guys cringe over plans to attend his son's circumcision while Rebecca struggles to throw an interesting retirement party for a very dull corporate employee.</desc><sub-title>For Real Men Only</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260517070749 -0400" stop="20260517073149 -0400"><title>The Big Bang Theory</title><desc>Sheldon's getting fired forces him to explore what life has to offer outside physics, leaving Leonard to take drastic action to snap his friend out of his funk.</desc><sub-title>The Luminous Fish Effect</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517052658 -0400" stop="20260517074030 -0400"><title>Fast Five</title><desc>Former cop Brian O'Conner partners with ex-con Dom Toretto on the opposite side of the law. Since Brian and Mia Toretto broke Dom out of custody, they've blown across many borders to elude authorities. Now backed into a corner in Rio de Janeiro, they must pull one last job in order to gain their freedom.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517120000 +0100" stop="20260517130000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>In a previous life, The Walnut Tree Inn in South Wales was a Michelin-starred restaurant known throughout Britain.    Under its new owners, Italian Francesco Mattioli, Gordon arrives to find the kitchen in chaos with no Head Chef and no customers.</desc><sub-title>The Walnut Tree Inn</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260517064126 -0400" stop="20260517073510 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>In the final programme, Gordon returns to Momma Cherri's Soul Food Shack, an intimate 40-seater in Brighton where he oversaw one of the most spectacular changes of fortune at a single venue. Owner Charita Jones was producing a menu of irresistible unique classics from the Deep South, but at the same facing financial disaster. The punters were missing, and so was her business acumen. But Gordon succeeded in shutting her out of the kitchen, getting the chef back on the boil and putting the soul back into the business.

Today Charita is fully-booked round the clock and bursting out of the Soul Shack to take on the 110-seater Momma Cherri's Big House. But expansion brings a different set of challenges, and she's still struggling to control her staff and manage her success. Has she got what it takes to make the next step up, or will she be forced to rethink her grand plans?</desc><sub-title>Momma Cherri's Soul Food Shack (Revisited)</sub-title></programme></tv>