<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260518014500 -0400" stop="20260518023000 -0400"><title>Stargate SG-1</title><desc>Carter must help keep a promising young cadet from throwing away a future at the SGC. O'Neill and Teal'c encounter a dangerous life form at an offworld research base.</desc><sub-title>Prodigy</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260518012627 -0400" stop="20260518030917 -0400"><title>Clerks</title><desc>Convenience and video store clerks Dante and Randal are sharp-witted, potty-mouthed and bored out of their minds. So in between needling customers, the counter jockeys play hockey on the roof, visit a funeral home and deal with their love lives.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260517232228 -0400" stop="20260518020026 -0400"><title>Indiana Jones and the Dial of Destiny</title><desc>Finding himself in a new era, and approaching retirement, Indy wrestles with fitting into a world that seems to have outgrown him. But as the tentacles of an all-too-familiar evil return in the form of an old rival, Indy must don his hat and pick up his whip once more to make sure an ancient and powerful artifact doesn't fall into the wrong hands.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260518063000 +0100" stop="20260518070000 +0100"><title>My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic</title><desc>While the Mane 6 are on a friendship retreat, Starlight Glimmer and Trixie lose Twilight's friendship map. Afraid her anger might get out of control, Starlight does a spell to contain it while they search for it.</desc><sub-title>All Bottled Up</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260518015413 -0400" stop="20260518022044 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The first visit of the week is in Blackpool, where there are unwanted guests in a bathroom and trouble at breakfast time.</desc><sub-title>Tower View Hotel</sub-title></programme></tv>