<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260519151500 -0400" stop="20260519154500 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>After an amazing date with Justin in Indianapolis, Leslie tries to impress him with a dinner party at her house.</desc><sub-title>Leslie's House</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260519151632 -0400" stop="20260519154045 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>George goes into denial when Max is thought to have dyslexia, and things only get worse when Angie suggests he may have it as well. Meanwhile, Ernie leaves home and moves in with George and Angie and takes on the job of minding his girlfriends kids while she enjoys life.</desc><sub-title>The Show Dyslexic</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260519145421 -0400" stop="20260519164116 -0400"><title>Who Framed Roger Rabbit</title><desc>'Toon star Roger is worried that his wife Jessica is playing pattycake with someone else, so the studio hires detective Eddie Valiant to snoop on her. But the stakes are quickly raised when Marvin Acme is found dead and Roger is the prime suspect. Groundbreaking interaction between the live and animated characters, and lots of references to classic animation.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260519193000 +0100" stop="20260519203500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>Jeremy drives the Mercedes McLaren SLR from London to Oslo, while Richard and James take the ferry across the North Sea. The Nissan Micra, Citro&#235;n C6 and Alfa Romeo Brera are featured, as is the Aston Martin DBR9. David Dimbleby is the Star in a Reasonably Priced Car.</desc><sub-title>Mercedes McLaren SLR vs. Boat</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260519144707 -0400" stop="20260519153355 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>Mike travels to Greenville, South Carolina, America and buys an all-black, empty, 1967 13-window Volkswagon Type 2 Deluxe. Also known as a "splitty" due to the two-pane split windscreen, this "bus" is rust-free but missing door cards, half the switch gear, headlining, a radio and has non-standard bucket seats.</desc><sub-title>Volkswagen Type 2</sub-title></programme></tv>