<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523141300 -0400" stop="20260523161500 -0400"><title>Red Notice</title><desc>An Interpol-issued Red Notice is a global alert to hunt and capture the world's most wanted. But when a daring heist brings together the FBI's top profiler and two rival criminals, there's no telling what will happen.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523151541 -0400" stop="20260523154027 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>The tables have turned inside 30 Rock: Liz is actually happy in her new relationship with Floyd while Jack finds his job may be in jeopardy after his televised fireworks fiasco prompts top GE man Don Geiss to warn he's got his eye on Jack's performance. Tracy vies for Geiss' attention, hoping to turn his feature film idea for Jefferson into a reality.</desc><sub-title>Corporate Crush</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523145950 -0400" stop="20260523164257 -0400"><title>The Polar Express</title><desc>This is the story of a young hero boy who boards on a powerful magical train that's headed to the North Pole and Santa Claus' home on Christmas Eve night. During this ride, he embarks on a journey of self-discovery which shows him that the wonder of life never fades for those who believe.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523200500 +0100" stop="20260523205000 +0100"><title>An Idiot Abroad</title><desc>It's the final part of the journey as Karl and Warwick get ready to make their way to China. A surprise makes sure that the series ends on a high.</desc><sub-title>The Short Way Round: China</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523152651 -0400" stop="20260523155140 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Prams, Factory-Built Homes, Wood Flutes, and Bicycle Tires and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Prams, Factory-Built Homes, Wood Flutes, Bicycle Tires</sub-title></programme></tv>