<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522100000 -0400" stop="20260522103000 -0400"><title>Frasier</title><desc>Frasier hires a shady lady lawyer to defend him from a litigious Donny, who blames him for Daphne running out on their wedding.</desc><sub-title>Legal Tender Love and Care</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522100718 -0400" stop="20260522103154 -0400"><title>Impractical Jokers</title><desc>Four friends compete to embarrass each other in the ultimate hidden camera showdown. In the season finale, the guys toy with customers at a candy store using bizarre party props, they all try their hands at nosing, and they break the rules of appropriate elevator etiquette.</desc><sub-title>Supercuts</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522093554 -0400" stop="20260522114700 -0400"><title>Deadpool &amp; Wolverine</title><desc>In this multiverse story Deadpool is approached by a man named Paradox who intends on vaporizing his entire universe because apparently it's not supposed to go on living without the now deceased hero Wolverine. Deadpool kidnaps another version of Wolverine to replace but this only results in Paradox banishing both Deadpool and Wolverine.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522150000 +0100" stop="20260522160000 +0100"><title>The Chase (2009)</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 127</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522100657 -0400" stop="20260522105402 -0400"><title>Wheeler Dealers</title><desc>The cheapest Astons in the UK are around &#163;16,000 but Mike decides he wants to spend less. By calling around some dealers, he finds a tired trade-in at a large main dealer. The car has interior water leaks and external oil leaks, it drives in a sloppy way, the engine is blowing, and it feels unloved. The dealer is willing to sell for &#163;13,500 but Mike tries to get him down further. By taking a faded masterpiece, turning back the clock and finishing everything to a very high standards Mike hopes to get absolute top dollar when he sells it on.</desc><sub-title>Aston Martin DB7</sub-title></programme></tv>