<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260522154500 -0400" stop="20260522161500 -0400"><title>Parks and Recreation</title><desc>When a possum bites the mayor's dog on a golf course, Leslie is asked to form a task force to catch the pesky animal. Meanwhile, Ron is upset when Mark refuses to bend the rules for him.</desc><sub-title>The Possum</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260522154040 -0400" stop="20260522181105 -0400"><title>Bad Boys II</title><desc>Miami is being flooded with ecstasy that's coming from Cuba through drug lord Johnny Tapia. Detectives Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett are on the case, and are determined to bring the man to justice. Additional drama is provided by friction with the DEA, which counts Marcus' younger sister Sydney among its agents, and from Marcus possibly transferring out of the department, leaving Mike without his longtime partner.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260522142449 -0400" stop="20260522160026 -0400"><title>Trolls</title><desc>After the monstrous Bergens invade Troll Village, Princess Poppy, the happiest Troll ever born, and overly-cautious, curmudgeonly outcast Branch set off on a journey to rescue her friends. Their mission is full of adventure and mishaps, as this mismatched duo try to tolerate each other long enough to get the job done.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260522205000 +0100" stop="20260522210500 +0100"><title>The Amazing World of Gumball</title><desc>Gumball and Darwin are wary of Anais' new friend, Josh, making her question his motives as well.</desc><sub-title>The Guy</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260522154302 -0400" stop="20260522163526 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Can a poppy-seed bagel tilt the results of a drug test? Can balloons carry a lawn chair? If you cover your body in gold paint, will you be able to breathe? Or could you die from it?</desc><sub-title>Poppy-Seed Drug Test</sub-title></programme></tv>