<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260531043000 -0400" stop="20260531052000 -0400"><title>The X-Files</title><desc>Widespread panic is caused in a small community after numerous deaths are linked to killer cockroaches, and a government agricultural agency is discovered to have set up a secret experiment involving insects.</desc><sub-title>War of the Coprophages</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260531051111 -0400" stop="20260531053825 -0400"><title>The Ricky Gervais Show</title><desc>More e-mail questions for Karl, such as: If Karl could talk to any animal, which would it be and what would he say? Highlights from Karl's diary, including why he doesn't like meetings, and why he and his girlfriend always get in an argument after she gets a haircut. In "Monkey News": A story from the 1950s about a gangster who bought a racehorse. When none of the jockeys wanted to be involved with him, he got a monkey to race the horse.</desc><sub-title>The Jockey</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260531035730 -0400" stop="20260531054228 -0400"><title>The Wizard of Oz</title><desc>Young Dorothy Gale and her dog Toto are swept away by a tornado from their Kansas farm to the magical Land of Oz and embark on a quest with three new friends to see the Wizard, who can return her to her home and fulfill the others' wishes.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260531101500 +0100" stop="20260531110000 +0100"><title>Escape to the Country</title><desc>Jules Hudson helps a couple to find a home with business potential. They have a budget of &#163;450,000 to spend on a rural Yorkshire property.

While in the county, Jules learns about the art of ploughing from a six nations champion.</desc><sub-title>North Yorkshire</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260531045657 -0400" stop="20260531052437 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>At the Angel Inn, Wangford, Suffolk, Kiwi couple Peter and Christine White offer up some down-under hospitality.

Next is Moap's Farm in Danehill, East Sussex, where Lesley Miller has a laissez-faire approach to cleaning, cooking and accommodation.

The competitors then head to Jabajak in Carmarthenshire, Wales. Here sisters Lorraine Lloyd and Amanda Stuart-Robson run a tight ship until they try sheep herding for their afternoon activity.

The last visit is to Gravesend, Kent where the Clarendon Royal Hotel, where Les Woollends plans a fun afternoon of cocktails.</desc><sub-title>From Angel Inn to the Clarendon Royal Hotel</sub-title></programme></tv>