<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260528000000 -0400" stop="20260528003000 -0400"><title>Two and a Half Men</title><desc>Jake and Eldridge finally graduate, but have neither skills nor ambition. Against Walden's warning how useless and dangerous the knaves are, when Alan comes begging for jobs for them, Walden's business partner Billy Stanhope insists on hiring them just to mind the servers farm. Alas, their porn addiction ends up bringing in a major virus. Just fired, they become easy prey for the military-recruiting sergeant, so he becomes Alan's next opponent.</desc><sub-title>Oh Look! Al-Qaeda!</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260528001221 -0400" stop="20260528003619 -0400"><title>Community</title><desc>Britta's April Fool's Day prank has disastrous consequences, but she refuses to confess that she was responsible. Annie and Shirley temporarily work as security guards, but both of them want to be the "bad cop."</desc><sub-title>The Science of Illusion</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260528000924 -0400" stop="20260528021539 -0400"><title>Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues</title><desc>With the 1970s behind him, Ron Burgundy, San Diego's former top-rated newsreader, returns to take New York City's first twenty-four-hour news channel by storm.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260528050000 +0100" stop="20260528053000 +0100"><title>The Joy of Painting</title><desc>Visiting artist, Ben Stahl, uses a more traditional painting method to bring out the coy loveliness of a little girl.</desc><sub-title>Portrait of Sally</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260528000552 -0400" stop="20260528003053 -0400"><title>Brain Games</title><desc>Discover how language is the closest thing humans have to telepathy and how you communicate without words every day. Guest Sri Sarma, a biomedical-engineer from Johns Hopkins University, leads a discovery of language and how humans create meaning.</desc><sub-title>Language</sub-title></programme></tv>