<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520174500 -0400" stop="20260520183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>A mother's sudden paralysis during a indoor rock-climbing incident leaves her daughter injured, and House's new team looking for a cure. Meanwhile, House organizes his new recruits' Secret Santa gift exchange... with a few twists of his own.</desc><sub-title>It's a Wonderful Lie</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520180119 -0400" stop="20260520182533 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Jake is interested in one of Rosa's perps, Doug Judy (Guest Star Craig Robinson, "The Office"), who has information about the "Pontiac Bandit," a car thief whom Jake has been tracking for years. Meanwhile, the station tries to accommodate a scooter-bound Charles' every need when he returns to work, but he proves to be too much to handle. And Captain Holt struggles to find a home for two puppies.</desc><sub-title>Pontiac Bandit</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260520172805 -0400" stop="20260520195411 -0400"><title>The Avengers</title><desc>When an unexpected enemy emerges and threatens global safety and security, Nick Fury, director of the international peacekeeping agency known as S.H.I.E.L.D., finds himself in need of a team to pull the world back from the brink of disaster. Spanning the globe, a daring recruitment effort begins!</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520230000 +0100" stop="20260520233000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Viv is visting a remand prisoner in prison and ends up being held hostage.  After being released she is told all his grevious's are false.   Melvin watches from a balcony in a shopping precinct as a man is approached by two black men and shot at point blank range.  He was going to collect a sniper's rifle at Paddington station.</desc><sub-title>The Visit</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520175349 -0400" stop="20260520181809 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 23</sub-title></programme></tv>