<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516193000 -0400" stop="20260516200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>Gene gets kicked out of the Ocean Avenue Hifi Emporium, but Louise takes matters into her own hands to defend Gene's honor. Teddy takes a handyman job at Jimmy Pesto's restaurant and tries to hide it from Bob.</desc><sub-title>Drumforgiven</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516185955 -0400" stop="20260516203739 -0400"><title>Wayne's World</title><desc>Two slacker friends try to promote their public-access cable show.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516192446 -0400" stop="20260516211532 -0400"><title>2 Fast 2 Furious</title><desc>EX LAPD cop Brian O'Conner (Paul Walker) teams up with his ex-con friend Roman Pearce (Tyrese Gibson) and works with undercover U.S. Customs Service agent Monica Fuentes (Eva Mendes) to bring Miami-based drug lord Carter Verone (Cole Hauser) down.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260517003000 +0100" stop="20260517010000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>The Decepticons work with a smuggler to take over a Mideast palace and begin acquiring plane parts for the construction of a air fortress. The Aerialbots head to the scene, but Slingshot and Sky Dive get into trouble. But a young man known as Hassan comes to their aid to help save the day.</desc><sub-title>Aerial Assault</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516193020 -0400" stop="20260516202321 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>In the penultimate programme, Gordon returns to La Riviera - now renamed Abstract - a fine dining restaurant in Inverness. Owned by multi-millionaire Barry Larson and costing &#163;8,000 a week to run, the place boasted top French chef Loic LeFebvre and an impeccably-trained kitchen staff, all of them on a mission to bring sophisticated French cooking to the home of the haggis.</desc><sub-title>Abstract (La Riviera Revisited)</sub-title></programme></tv>