<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523141300 -0400" stop="20260523161500 -0400"><title>Red Notice</title><desc>An Interpol-issued Red Notice is a global alert to hunt and capture the world's most wanted. But when a daring heist brings together the FBI's top profiler and two rival criminals, there's no telling what will happen.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523130820 -0400" stop="20260523145044 -0400"><title>Shaun of the Dead</title><desc>Shaun (Simon Pegg) doesn't have a very good day, so he decides to turn his life around by getting his ex to take him back, but he times it for right in the middle of what may be a zombie apocalypse. But for him, it's an opportunity to show everyone he knows how useful he is by saving them all. All he has to do is survive, and get his ex back.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523132018 -0400" stop="20260523145950 -0400"><title>Bolt</title><desc>Bolt, an American white shepherd, has lived his whole life on the set of his action TV show, where he believes he has superpowers. When separated from the studio by accident, he meets a female alley cat named Mittens and a hamster named Rhino. He's trying to find the way home, to the studio. Along the way, he learns that he doesn't have superpowers and that the show is not real.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523190000 +0100" stop="20260523200500 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>Jeremy tests the BMW 535d. Richard goes to Iceland to see whether is it possible to drive over a lake. James travels to Dubai to test the Bentley Continental Flying Spur. The boys test various off-road toys (buggies, ATV quad bikes, hover-crafts, etc.) to see which is the most fun. Big Brother host Davina McCall and Mark Webber are the Stars In A Reasonably Priced Car.</desc><sub-title>Can a Jeep Drive Across a Lake?</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523133951 -0400" stop="20260523143302 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Could prisoners really have escaped Alcatraz without a trace? Does a duck's quack echo? Can a stud finder really prove if human beings have been guinea pigs in mind-control experiments.</desc><sub-title>Alcatraz Escape</sub-title></programme></tv>