<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520000000 -0400" stop="20260520003000 -0400"><title>Two and a Half Men</title><desc>As part of his divorce closure and start of a new single dating life, Walden redecorates the beach house. When Charlie's piano is taken away, already jealous Alan also turns melancholic and ends up incarnating his dearly missed brother, getting drunk and picking up girls as Charlie, down to his name and Bermudas. Jake feels insecure, squashed between two fellow losers turning into Charlies.</desc><sub-title>Thank You for the Intercourse</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520000403 -0400" stop="20260520002757 -0400"><title>George Lopez</title><desc>As George gets ready for Halloween, Carmen falls into a depression after her best friend, Toby, moves away. After George 'letting Carmen find her own way' doesn't work, Angie gets her on the cheerleader team so she can make new friends.</desc><sub-title>Halloween Cheer</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260519234946 -0400" stop="20260520003858 -0400"><title>The Garden of Words</title><desc>On a rainy morning in Tokyo, 15-year-old Takao, an aspiring shoemaker, decides to skip class to sketch designs in a beautiful garden. This is where he meets Yukari, a beautiful yet mysterious woman. They strike an unlikely friendship.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520050000 +0100" stop="20260520053000 +0100"><title>The Joy of Painting</title><desc>Bob Ross captures the beauty of Alaska on canvas: clear skies, soft cottony clouds, snow covered mountains and breathtaking crystal lake.</desc><sub-title>Cool Waters</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520002051 -0400" stop="20260520011501 -0400"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Gordon takes on an ex-boxer and his feisty wife whose barroom brawls are scaring away customers 

Gordon might be famed for his aggression in the kitchen but he meets his match this week as Kitchen Nightmares heads to rural Wales

The Fish &amp; Anchor restaurant and bar near Lampeter is run by a couple of bruisers, ex-boxer Mike and his mouthy wife Caron.

A self taught cook, Mike is a one-man pressure cooker in the kitchen as he struggles to cope with a menu too vast and wide ranging for his skills.

While Mike gets steamed up in the kitchen, Carol's getting hot under the collar in the restaurant. Her unique front-of-house management style includes abusing the customers and her husband in equal measure. Every night they go twelve rounds with the local clientele who are fast deserting them to the tune of a &#163;1,000 per week loss.

Enter Gordon, who finds himself cast as marriage counsellor in a culinary battlefield. It&#8217;s a last-ditch attempt to reverse the restaurant&#8217;s disastrous reputation and put some love back into the kitchen as well as on plates. Will Mike take on board a last-minute reality check in the fight of his life, or stay on the ropes and sink?</desc><sub-title>The Fish &amp; Anchor</sub-title></programme></tv>