<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520070000 -0400" stop="20260520073000 -0400"><title>The King of Queens</title><desc>Carrie asks Deacon and Kelly to accompany her and Doug to Florida for their visit with the in-laws so that they'll be forced to stay at a hotel instead of with Doug's parents. What looks like a perfect vacation turns into a nightmare when spring breakers invade the hotel, forcing Carrie and Doug to reconsider their future accommodations when visiting the folks. Adding to the misery is the great disappointment shown by Doug's mom over the fact that no one is staying at her house.</desc><sub-title>Precedent Nixin'</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520065803 -0400" stop="20260520072133 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>Liz and Jenna work on their dating game when they're beguiled by two very different MSNBC staffers: a brainy geek and a brawny hunk, but cerebral Liz finds it strange that she's more interested in the attractive one. Meanwhile, Kenneth and Jack switch roles.</desc><sub-title>The Head and the Hair</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260520043241 -0400" stop="20260520075758 -0400"><title>The Godfather Part II</title><desc>The continuing saga of the Corleone crime family tells the story of a young Vito Corleone growing up in Sicily and in 1910s New York; and follows Michael Corleone in the 1950s as he attempts to expand the family business into Las Vegas, Hollywood and Cuba.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520120000 +0100" stop="20260520130000 +0100"><title>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares</title><desc>Mexican-born Israel and his English partner Tara have sunk a cool &#163;150,000 of their own money into their trendy cafe bar D-Place, which offers a vast selection of fusion cuisine.

They believed they had found the WINNING FORMULA: great place, great music, great service, great food... and all at the right price.

Sounds promising... but from there on it's all DOWNHILL.

For the first two years, it all went swimmingly as Israel built up a mini-empire of five businesses... but the success didn't last long. Just three years later and they are all GONE - only D-Place remains and it's hanging by a thread.

It's a 24-carat NIGHTMARE.

The staff are at WAR, the plastic food is DIRE, the customers have evaporated, the restaurant is losing MONEY and the owners are at their WITS END. Something simply has to give or everyone is out of a job.

Faced with dysfunctional staff and a disastrous menu, Gordon is about to face the LONGEST WEEK of his professional life. Can he quell the panic, banish the deep fa</desc><sub-title>D-Place</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520061730 -0400" stop="20260520071015 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 23</sub-title></programme></tv>