<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260528174500 -0400" stop="20260528183000 -0400"><title>House</title><desc>The team deals with an organ donor whose organs prove fatal, and the two surviving patients. Meanwhile, House hires a private detective to spy on Wilson, but hears a few things about himself that he'd rather not.</desc><sub-title>Not Cancer</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260528180433 -0400" stop="20260528182713 -0400"><title>The Big Bang Theory</title><desc>Sheldon becomes Leonard's teacher in order to understand football, while an incident with flying a kite threatens Howard and Raj's friendship.</desc><sub-title>The Cornhusker Vortex</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260528180841 -0400" stop="20260528193723 -0400"><title>Aqua Teen Hunger Force Colon Movie Film for Theaters</title><desc>An action epic that explores the origins of Master Shake, Frylock, and Meatwad, better known as the Aqua Teen Hunger Force, who somehow become pitted in a battle over an immortal piece of exercise equipment.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260528230000 +0100" stop="20260528233000 +0100"><title>The Bill</title><desc>Tosh and Carver are in a car waiting for a suspect who gets away after pinching a mailman's bike. Suspect's wife has been rumoured as doing modeling work. Suspect hangs off the balcony of a 5th floor flat and swings to the floor below. Taffy is sent to investigate an old lady who isn't answering her door. she died unexpectedly. Reg has been talking to Conway and then tries talking to Frazer. He wants to resign as collator. Reg has lovebites on his neck. He snaps at Taffy after Ramsey and Stamp have been having a go at him first. All for nothing as the lady he had been seeing didn't want to see him again. June is being encouraged to go for her sergeant's exams by all the sergeants on the relief.</desc><sub-title>Back On The Streets</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260528174329 -0400" stop="20260528183640 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Is the photo of a light plane, with precise, clean tears on the side, genuine? Was it the work of the jilted lover, who took to her ex's plane with a chainsaw and a taste for vengeance?</desc><sub-title>Shredded Plane</sub-title></programme></tv>