<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260529193000 -0400" stop="20260529200000 -0400"><title>Bob's Burgers</title><desc>When the Belcher kids participate in a beach clean-up for Wagstaff Volunteer Day, Louise gets drawn into a battle of wits with Mr. Fischoeder; Teddy surprises Bob and Linda with a new look.</desc><sub-title>Beach, Please</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260529194343 -0400" stop="20260529200751 -0400"><title>Community</title><desc>Greendale Community College is transformed into an apocalyptic war zone when the dean promises the winner of a paintball competition priority registration, and it could fan the flames of sexual tension between Jeff and Britta.</desc><sub-title>Modern Warfare</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260529190840 -0400" stop="20260529204704 -0400"><title>Kung Fu Panda 4</title><desc>After Po is tapped to become the Spiritual Leader of the Valley of Peace, he needs to find and train a new Dragon Warrior, while a wicked sorceress plans to re-summon all the master villains whom Po has vanquished to the spirit realm.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530003000 +0100" stop="20260530010000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc>Both Autobots and Decepticons are facing tough times as they are in need of the element called Cybertonium. The Decepticons quickly get as much as they need, but the only way for the Autobots to get it is to rely on The Dinobots, who have been unaffected by all this. However, the Dinobots have been getting annoyed with The Autobots lately and leave them.</desc><sub-title>Desertion of the Dinobots (1)</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260529193728 -0400" stop="20260529200238 -0400"><title>How It's Made</title><desc>This episode demonstrates the production processes for Ceramic Fireplaces, Synthetic Corks, and Parking Garage Floor Slabs and shows how each is made.</desc><sub-title>Ceramic Fireplaces, Synthetic Corks, Parking Garage Floor Slabs</sub-title></programme></tv>