<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260520114500 -0400" stop="20260520123000 -0400"><title>Escape to the Country</title><desc>Jonnie Irwin helps a couple of golf fanatics to find a slice of rural heaven in the Cotswolds. With a budget of &#163;500,000, are they ready to leave the urban bustle of London? Away from the house hunt, Jonnie meets the bovine lawnmowers restoring a precious Cotswold habitat.</desc><sub-title>Cotswolds</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260520113331 -0400" stop="20260520115828 -0400"><title>The Goldbergs (2013)</title><desc>Barry signs up for a holiday talent show at the school, but karate isn't approved as a talent; Pops coerces Erica into performing in the show.</desc><sub-title>Kara-Te</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260520095141 -0400" stop="20260520115051 -0400"><title>Children Who Chase Lost Voices</title><desc>A coming of age story involving young love and a mysterious music, coming from a crystal radio left as a memento by an absent father, that leads a young heroine deep into a hidden world.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260520164500 +0100" stop="20260520170000 +0100"><title>The Amazing World of Gumball</title><desc>The Singing: The town of Elmore becomes an all-singing, all-dancing mash up. Everyone has a song inside them, but do they really need to be heard? / The Best: No matter what Gumball does, Carmen thinks she knows better. Gumball attempts to gain the moral high ground but fails spectacularly. He decides that self-improvement isn't his style. The only option he has left is to bring Carmen down to his level.</desc><sub-title>The Best</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260520113127 -0400" stop="20260520115834 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The second visit of the week is to Treberthan in Cornwall where Kathryn Langley and Trevor Burnell nearly come unstuck at breakfast and are left with some explaining to do.</desc><sub-title>Treberthan</sub-title></programme></tv>