<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260530014500 -0400" stop="20260530023000 -0400"><title>Stargate SG-1</title><desc>After the death of Omoc, the Tollan assert that they are now ready to trade technology with the Tau'ri. Negotiations go smoothly, a little too smoothly. SG-1, with the assistance of Narim, investigate the death of Omoc and the Curia's deception of the Tollan people.</desc><sub-title>Between Two Fires</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260530015454 -0400" stop="20260530021909 -0400"><title>The Great North</title><desc>Judy's murder mystery party doesn't go exactly as planned; Alyson invites herself on a date with Beef.</desc><sub-title>Skidmark Holmes Adventure</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260530014309 -0400" stop="20260530041141 -0400"><title>Goodfellas</title><desc>Henry Hill recounts his life in the mob, from his teenage years to his eventual downfall. Immersed in organized crime, he experiences wealth, power, and violence alongside friends Jimmy Conway and Tommy DeVito. The film blends crime, drama, and dark humor, exploring loyalty, ambition, betrayal, and the consequences of criminal life. Themes of family, morality, and the fleeting nature of power underpin the story.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530063000 +0100" stop="20260530070000 +0100"><title>My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic</title><desc>When Rainbow Dash&#8217;s favorite author, A.K. Yearling, announces her retirement, she convinces Pinkie Pie to go on a quest to find out if the Daring Do book series will be closed forever.</desc><sub-title>Daring Done?</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260530014332 -0400" stop="20260530023544 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>The team tries out a myth of farm workers' pants igniting, using materials from fertilizer to explosives, while the boys waste money on nifty fuel-saving devices found on the Internet, and remind us that biodiesel (cooking oil!) is a semi-viable fuel alternative.</desc><sub-title>Exploding Pants</sub-title></programme></tv>