<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260516141300 -0400" stop="20260516161500 -0400"><title>Red Notice</title><desc>An Interpol-issued Red Notice is a global alert to hunt and capture the world's most wanted. But when a daring heist brings together the FBI's top profiler and two rival criminals, there's no telling what will happen.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260516142343 -0400" stop="20260516144730 -0400"><title>30 Rock</title><desc>Now that major changes have occurred on the The Girlie Show, Liz struggles to bring everyone and everything together. However, despite his erratic behavior, Tracy manages to bring everything to order.</desc><sub-title>The Aftermath</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260516140356 -0400" stop="20260516154940 -0400"><title>Toy Story 3</title><desc>The toys are mistakenly delivered to a day-care center instead of the attic right before Andy leaves for college, and it's up to Woody to convince the other toys that they weren't abandoned and to return home.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260516191500 +0100" stop="20260516203000 +0100"><title>Top Gear</title><desc>Jeremy makes a splash when he drives a Rolls Royce Silver Shadow MK1 to the opening of a local swimming pool. Richard drives the Aston Martin DB9 Volante and James goes back to the 1970's to drive the Maserati Bora. The German-built retro-styled Weissman MF3is compared to the TVR Tuscan MKII. There's also a look at the Batmobile. Christopher Ecclestone is the Star in a Reasonably Priced Car.</desc><sub-title>Clarkson Opens a Public Pool With a Rolls-Royce</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260516143118 -0400" stop="20260516145931 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The B&amp;Bers meet for the last time and thrash out their differences and find out who's this week's winner.

Feedback includes criticism of a badly positioned tea tray, a hot chocolate storm, and accusations of over-enthusiastic hosting.</desc><sub-title>Payment Day</sub-title></programme></tv>