<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260529210000 -0400" stop="20260529220000 -0400"><title>Salvage Hunters</title><desc>Drew uncovers plenty of rare items at a Welsh country house turned wedding venue, but the negotiations are intense. The chaps scour a one-man salvage operation near Coventry. Wroxall Estate boasts its own cathedral and several promising storage sheds. A self-confessed hoarder, Tim has amassed a staggering array of stock but is reluctant to let anything go.</desc><sub-title>Episode 7</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260529212115 -0400" stop="20260529214522 -0400"><title>Archer (2009)</title><desc>Archer is faced with a dilemma when his murdered fiance, Katya, miraculously reappears. In Krieger's lab.</desc><sub-title>Skin Game</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260529204704 -0400" stop="20260529221118 -0400"><title>Toy Story</title><desc>A cowboy doll is profoundly jealous when a new spaceman action figure supplants him as the top toy in a boy's bedroom. When circumstances separate them from their owner, the duo have to put aside their differences to return to him.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260530023000 +0100" stop="20260530030000 +0100"><title>Friends</title><desc>Emily's surprised remark she wouldn't want her ex-lovers on the wedding unlike Ross who invites Rachel starts him reminiscing about him getting and losing Rachel. Everybody gets an invitation, but Phoebe may not fly during her pregnancy and Rachel feels it's just too hard for her, after reminiscing as well about her with and without Ross.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Invitation</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260529212330 -0400" stop="20260529221456 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Adam and Jamie do a little painting and detonating when they try to blow open a home-improvement myth. Grant, Tory and Kari explore if it is possible to manipulate someone's mind remotely.</desc><sub-title>Mind Control</sub-title></programme></tv>