<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523131500 -0400" stop="20260523134500 -0400"><title>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title><desc>Rosa and Amy track down a killer who's managed to elude them for seven years; Terry helps Jake with his wedding chores; Holt and his rival try to convince each other to resign from the campaign for Commissioner.</desc><sub-title>White Whale</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523130820 -0400" stop="20260523145044 -0400"><title>Shaun of the Dead</title><desc>Shaun (Simon Pegg) doesn't have a very good day, so he decides to turn his life around by getting his ex to take him back, but he times it for right in the middle of what may be a zombie apocalypse. But for him, it's an opportunity to show everyone he knows how useful he is by saving them all. All he has to do is survive, and get his ex back.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523111233 -0400" stop="20260523132018 -0400"><title>Red One</title><desc>After Santa Claus -- Code Name: RED ONE -- is kidnapped, the North Pole's Head of Security (Dwayne Johnson) must team up with the world's most infamous bounty hunter and notorious hacker (Chris Evans) in a globe-trotting, action-packed mission to save Christmas.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523180000 +0100" stop="20260523184500 +0100"><title>House</title><desc>A patient with AIDS stalks House to get him to take his case; House and Stacy stalk a mouse in her attic; and Cameron faces a health scare of her own.</desc><sub-title>Hunting</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523131107 -0400" stop="20260523133951 -0400"><title>Four in a Bed</title><desc>The B&amp;B owners gather to find out how much they've been paid, and to reveal the winner.

Melvyn and Sindy interrogate their guests over the criticism in their feedback. Gill and Peter from the Victory bristle at the negative feedback and two underpayments. Butterfly Dave gets in a flap over a series of large underpayments. And Wayne and Deborah's payments leave the competition result in the balance.</desc><sub-title>Payment Day, Week 4</sub-title></programme></tv>