<tv generator-info-url="https://github.com/amazeyourself/m3u"><channel id="whiplash"><display-name>Whiplash</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplash" start="20260523023000 -0400" stop="20260523025500 -0400"><title>Friends</title><desc>Emily's surprised remark she wouldn't want her ex-lovers on the wedding unlike Ross who invites Rachel starts him reminiscing about him getting and losing Rachel. Everybody gets an invitation, but Phoebe may not fly during her pregnancy and Rachel feels it's just too hard for her, after reminiscing as well about her with and without Ross.</desc><sub-title>The One with the Invitation</sub-title></programme><channel id="whiplashii"><display-name>Whiplash II</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplash2.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashii" start="20260523023716 -0400" stop="20260523042952 -0400"><title>School of Rock</title><desc>Fired from his band and hard up for cash, guitarist and vocalist Dewey Finn finagles his way into a job as a fifth-grade substitute teacher at a private school, where he secretly begins teaching his straight-A students the finer points of rock 'n' roll and the power of sticking it to the man. But as the school&#8217;s stern principal closes in and the Battle of the Bands looms, Dewey risks everything to prove that rock 'n' roll can change lives.</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="whiplashcinema"><display-name>Whiplash Cinema</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/whiplashcinema.png" /></channel><programme channel="whiplashcinema" start="20260523010000 -0400" stop="20260523024535 -0400"><title>Cars 3</title><desc>Blindsided by a new generation of blazing-fast racers, the legendary Lightning McQueen is suddenly pushed out of the sport he loves. To get back in the game, he will need the help of an eager young race technician with her own plan to win, inspiration from the late Fabulous Hudson Hornet, and a few unexpected turns. Proving that #95 isn't through yet will test the heart of a champion on Piston Cup Racing's biggest stage!</desc><sub-title /></programme><channel id="windowtv"><display-name>Window TV</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/windowtv.png" /></channel><programme channel="windowtv" start="20260523073000 +0100" stop="20260523080000 +0100"><title>The Transformers</title><desc /><sub-title>Episode 82</sub-title></programme><channel id="atlas"><display-name>Atlas</display-name><icon src="https://whiplash.cc/assets/img/channels/atlas.png" /></channel><programme channel="atlas" start="20260523021401 -0400" stop="20260523030646 -0400"><title>MythBusters</title><desc>Jamie and Adam test whether a penny dropped from a skyscraper will embed in concrete and whether it is possible to pick up radio signals through tooth fillings. They also examine several myths surrounding microwave ovens.</desc><sub-title>Penny Drop</sub-title></programme></tv>